Sorry, I'm late.
抱歉 我来晚了
I ran into some trouble.
我碰到了点麻烦
So,
那么
what kind of fire are you going to show me?
你会为我展现怎样的火焰呢
According to my friends, I'm like a moth flying into flame.
我的朋友们都说 我就像一只扑火的飞蛾
If it's a beautiful flame, it's worth flying into.
希望你展现的火焰 能值得我扑身于其中
(Dead Mount, Death Play)
《尸体如山的死亡游戏》
(Episode 23: The Declaration) What's wrong?
(#23 The Declaration-宣战-) 你怎么了
Jackpot.
猜对了
As expected of Mr. Hosorogi.
真不愧是细吕木先生
Here are some facts about the fire that happened 100 years ago.
这是一百年前那场火灾的资料
You know, about that house we went to yesterday.
上面记载着我们昨天去过的 那个房子的情况
Who are you?
请问你们是谁
Oh, pardon us.
啊 不好意思
We do not belong to any suspicious person.
那个 我们不是坏人
This is my ID.
这是我的证件
We are police from the Community Safety Division.
我们是生活安全科的警察
We're interviewing people in the area.
作为地方调查的一环 我们想问您一些事
According to that man,
据那个男人所说
he has been asked by the property owner to manage the home.
是房主委托他管理那个房子的
The owner confirmed
而我们也实际向房主确认过了
that the guy wasn't lying.
那个男人的身份也没有造假
Yes.
是的
That's why we weren't able to do much digging back there.
所以那时我们没能挖到更多的情报
But with this documentation, we might be able to do something.
不过只要有这些资料 就应该有办法查清楚了
Thank you, Mr. Hosorogi.
谢谢您 细吕木先生
I will definitely find out the truth.
我一定会查清真相
And reveal the enigmatic mask of Sabaramond.
并揭开塞巴拉隆多的神秘面纱的
By the way, Clarissa, what are we doing about tomorrow?
对了 克拉丽莎 我们明天要怎么办
This time we'll only be watching.
这次就静观其变吧
Is that okay?
没关系吗
I want to get a grasp of exactly how far he'll go.
我想知道他究竟能做到什么地步
Of course, as the mediator, we'll at least fulfill the bare minimum of our promise.
不过作为中介屋 我还是会履行约定的
Watching over them will require appropriate preparations too.
静观其变也需要做好相应的准备
What are those three up to?
那三个人有什么动作吗
They made contact with someone who appeared to be Solitaire last night.
他们昨晚与一名 像是雪天鸦的男性有过接触
But there's been no further movement since.
在那之后他们就没有其他动作了
Are they hostile toward Solitaire?
他们与雪天鸦是敌对关系吗
The mob with the umbrellas…
这些撑伞的群众是…
Fire.
火
Solitaire.
雪天鸦
Could it be Fire-breathing Bug?
该不会是赴火之虫吧
It's almost time.
马上就到约定的时间了
That Taipei guy is coming, right?
那个叫太贝的家伙会来吧
Honestly, I don't quite understand who those three people are.
说实话我不太清楚 那三人究竟是何方神圣
But if I can get him to understand
但我们必须让尊先生他们重新认识到
that they're a threat to Shinoyama's existence.
那三人会对四乃山家造成威胁
And we need to get their help.
并获得他们的帮助才行
What happens after we save Polka?
救回波尔卡后我们该怎么办呢
I think I should be able to hold back the elf.
我想我应该能想办法 压制住精灵 之后…
That's where me and Xiaoyu come in. Hee hee.
就轮到我和小幽出场了对吧 嘻嘻
I've almost perfected my right arm for how to use it.
我大概掌握了右手的用法
I've also been training with that tiger earlier.
我刚才也一直在跟那只老虎做训练
Hey, listen.
各位 听我说
Even in shark films, it's those characters without names who die first.
鲨鱼电影中没有名字的角色 通常死得最早
Where is this coming from?
你怎么突然说这个
I think we ought to think about how we'll refer to
我想说我们应该怎样在称呼上
the real Polka versus you.
区分你和真正的波尔卡比较好
It could get confusing when we're in the thick of it.
说得也是 以后说不定会搞混的
"Corpse God", I know it's your name,
虽然你被人称为尸神殿
but it is hard to pronounce in Japanese.
不过你的本名很难用日语发音对吧
Polka?
波尔卡
Sorry, I lied.
抱歉 我之前说谎了
True, it's a little hard to say,
确实有些难发音
but not impossible to pronounce.
但也不是没办法念出来
It just reminds me of bad times,
因为这会让我想起不好的往事
so I don't like to say my own name.
所以我只是不想说出来而已
But this is as good an opportunity as any, so I'll tell it to you now.
那我就趁这次的机会告诉你们吧
My name is…
我的名字是…
Wait.
等等
The real Polka is on the move.
真正的波尔卡的位置开始移动了
The two women
两个女人
have left the hotel.
从饭店出来了
Two out of the three, huh?
三人中的两人吗
What about the other one?
还有一个人呢
What's wrong?
怎么了
Hey, I came back to see you, just as I promised.
嗨 我按照约定过来了
This time, as a friend.
这次我是以朋友的身份过来的
Why has this guy come to find us in particular?
这家伙为什么要特地来找我们
Hey, wait a minute.
喂 等一下
If you came in via the building's entrance,
如果你从大楼正门进来
then I should've known.
我应该会知道才对
Ah, yes. I made use of the underground passage.
这个啊 我借用了一下地下通道
No need to be so on guard.
你不用这么紧张
I simply came to be your friend.
我只是来跟你交朋友的
My friend?
跟我交朋友吗
Yes.
是的
There are so few people in this world who can understand me.
在目前的这个世界上 能理解我的人很少
The same goes for those
理解你…
who can understand you, or rather, your power, right?
不 理解你的力量的人也很少对吧
Has he already figured out that I come from another world?
他已经确定我是来自异世界的人了吗
You must've gone through life so confused.
想必你也是一直抱持着疑问 生活过来的吧
I feel sorry for you.
真可怜
But your power isn't something to curse.
但是你并不需要去讨厌这份力量
It's something to be proud of.
你应该为其感到骄傲才对
Because it's a power inherited from your mother.
这是你从你母亲那里继承而来的
And it's from the same world as mine.
跟我属于同一个世界的力量
What are you talking about?
你在说什么
Your mother, Kanon Shinoyama,
你的母亲 四乃山卡农
that is the descendant of a family that possesses the elf eye…
不 应该说是 具有精灵之眼的一族的后裔
Canomuchelin Redrazalf.
卡农穆榭林雷托拉沙鲁夫
What did you
你刚才…
just say?
说什么
Polka, what's wrong with you?
波尔卡 你怎么了
I'd always wondered
我一直都有个疑问
why I was reborn into this body.
为什么我会转生到这个身体上
I should have more deeply probed Polka's memories sooner.
要是我能早点触及 波尔卡的记忆深处就好了
This faint memory, deep down.
那些位于深处的虚无飘渺的记忆
A memory so distant that it seems in danger of disappearing.
那些快要消失殆尽的遥远回忆
The name of the person I couldn't save in the end.
那是我最终都没能拯救到的 那个人的名字
I never thought I would hear this name in this world.
没想到我会在这个世界听到这个名字
Did you finally get to live out your last days in peace here?
你最后有过上平稳的生活吗
Mother.
母亲
The one condition decided at the time my rebirth spell was invoked
我发动转生术时 所选定的唯一一个条件
was that I possess the fresh corpse
那就是我只能将灵魂附在
of someone of my race.
跟自己是同一种族的新鲜尸体上
To think that would link me to my mother, who had somehow come to this world.
但不知为何 我和过去来到 这个世界的我的母亲产生了联系
Polka.
波尔卡
Did you also see it?
原来你也能看到吗
Perhaps mother taught you all kinds of things too.
你也从我母亲那里 知晓了各种各样的事情吧
There's a lot I want to talk to you about.
我有好多话想和你说
I have to have another proper face-to-face talk with you.
我得跟他再次好好谈谈才行
So,
所以
give Polka back.
请你把波尔卡还给我
Polka, my friend, and also my little brother.
把我的朋友 我的弟弟还给我
Little brother?
把你的弟弟还给你
Was I mistaken?
是我误会了什么吗
But his appearance is, without a doubt, Polka Shinoyama.
他的外表明明是四乃山波尔卡 可内心却不一样
Is he saying what's on the inside is different? The soul…
那么他真正的内心是…灵魂是…
That shark?
那个…鲨鱼吗
No matter.
算了
The real talk starts now.
接下来我就进入正题了
If you've come the other side of the sky,
天空的彼端
the other world,
如果你来自异世界
and you have something to do with this mark,
而且还与这个记号有关的话
then you're affiliated with the empire.
那你就是与帝国有关的人
So let's join forces
让我们携手一起将我们的敌人
and exterminate that bug together.
将那些虫子都驱除掉吧
Fire-breathing Bug.
赴火之虫
Ah, I knew you'd quick on the uptake. That's good.
哎呀你理解得很快嘛 我很高兴
There's one thing I want to ask you.
我有一件事问你
Do you know Mr. Sabaramond…
你知道塞巴拉隆多先生…
No, Mr. Arius?
不 你知道亚里乌斯先生吗
Oh, this is a surprise.
哇 真让我吃惊
Are you an acquaintance of his?
你该不会认识他吧
You didn't answer my question.
你没有回答我的问题
I know of him.
我确实知道有这么一个人
But I've never met him.
但我没见过他
Because I'm his product.
毕竟我是他的产物
It seems two of the three are heading to the building too.
那三人中的两人 似乎正在朝波尔卡的大楼接近
Handle them as you please. It's that woman that you had a scuffle with.
她们随你处置 那个跟你交过手的女人就在其中
Understood.
遵命
I'll ask you plain and simple.
我就开门见山地问你了
Will you join our organization?
要不要加入我们的组织
I must decline.
恕我拒绝
That was quick.
你回答得好快
What I want is a peaceful life.
我想要的是平稳的生活
I don't know what your goal is,
虽然我不知道你们的目的
but your methods clash with mine.
但我无法赞同你们的做法
I'd rather take Solitaire over you.
你们甚至都不如怪人雪天鸦
Ah, is this because of Habaki?
啊 幅木真是干了不少好事啊
He was acting on his own.
那些事都是那家伙擅自做的
Mr. Arius didn't flee from his responsibilities as a ruler.
亚里乌斯先生 可不会逃避他作为上级的责任
Just as I thought. You know Arius well.
你果然很清楚亚里乌斯的事
Though I have never met him,
虽然我没见过他
but it pisses me off that you hold him in higher regard than me.
但你说那家伙在我之上 这让我有点不爽
Especially since he's the one who abandoned me in this world.
毕竟就是那家伙 把我抛弃在这个世界的
Abandoned?
抛弃…
It appears that our discussion has come to a halt.
看来我们已经没办法好好谈话了
I want you to show me your powers.
所以 我想见识一下你的力量
I am even more intrigued by the fact
既然你不是四乃山波尔卡
that you are not Polka Shinoyama.
那就更让我感兴趣了
Fine. All your yapping was a real help.
好 多亏你说了这么久
It gave me plenty of time to invoke my spell.
我才能从容不迫地准备好魔法
-Those are? -Bones?
-这是… -骨头
Right!
没错
This is no elf summoning or general sorcery!
这不是精灵术或泛用类的魔法
If the texts from the other world are correct, then this is…
如果那边世界的情报 是正确的话 那这就是
Necromancy!
死灵术
Could it be
不会吧
Easlies Swordfrail?
他是伊斯莉丝索多弗雷尔吗
No, this is different!
不 不对
There are only three powerful necromancers by Arius's side.
亚里乌斯的身边 只有三位强大的死灵术士
Judging by his attitude and what he's said so far…
从他至今为止的态度 和他说的话中可以推测出…
You're…
你是…
The fourth rank, aren't you?
第四席吗
One of the empire's leading imperial court sorcerers,
你是帝国宫廷魔法师的干部
Corpse God?
尸神殿吗
I felt a chill.
总觉得好冷
Maybe I'm a little too nervous.
是我太紧张了吗
For some reason, I feel like I've gotten involved in something totally huge.
总觉得自己被卷进了非常大的事件里
But that just means I'm close to a big scoop!
不过这也说明我离大新闻很近了
I can't give up now!
为了大新闻 我要加油
Yahoo!
嘿嘿噢
It has…begun.
开始了…吗
Now, to…settle it.
就在这里…做个…了断
We will…place our will…into that girl.
在那个小孩身上… 寄予…我们的意识
Then we will arrive…
如此…我们…便能抵达
at the bug's nest…
需要烧毁的…虫穴
Hey.
嗨
Mind if ask you a couple questions?
可以请你回答几个问题吗
Mr. Fire-breathing Bug.
赴火之虫先生
Where are you heading with those umbrellas
天气这么好 你们却都撑着伞
on such a clear day?
这是要去哪呢
Well, well. Hello, Mr. Detective.
哎呀哎呀 刑警先生
Thanks for the other day.
前些日子真是多谢您的关照
But putting that aside,
对了 您有什么事吗
what's the big idea? You suddenly show up and call me "Fire-breathing Bug."
您突然过来跟我们说什么赴火之虫…
If I remember right, that's the name of the arsonist who's been
这好像是会让社会人心惶惶的
wreaking havoc in town lately, isn't it?
那个纵火犯的名字吧
Yes.
是的
But that isn't the name of a single individual.
不过 赴火之虫并不是 某一个人的名字
By that time that name got around,
而且这个名字传开的时候
the ones who originally should have been called that were no more.
原本叫这个名字的家伙们 都已经不在了
A certain somebody kindly left behind some records that indicate
这是我从某个人留下的资料中得知的
some sort of human experiment took place in this house.
这个房子里曾做过某种人体实验
Haigawara Mitsu and Toura Takejirou.
灰河原三津和户里竹治郎
Prisoners of Sabaramond's human experiments
那个名为塞巴拉隆多的组织
were investigated for homicide.
在人体实验的最后 所引起的监禁杀人事件中
The two survivors
幸存的那两个人
were the start of you, Fire-breathing Bug, weren't they?
才是你们赴火之虫的始祖吧
What you just said is totally lost on me.
我完全听不懂您刚才说的话
If you do not have a warrant,
您如果没有搜查令的话
I'm afraid I can't help you.
那就恕我无法继续奉陪了
Well, just let me ask one more thing.
好 那我就再问你一个问题吧
A doctor at our station saw those records and had this to say about them.
我们的医生在看到那份资料后 是这么说的
Perhaps these experiences were meant to instill a specific pattern of reasoning.
这恐怕是在人身上植入 “非常理”的实验吧
Interesting.
真是有意思
Their method combined unique voices and sound waves
通过组合特殊的声音和音波
to drill condensed information into the human brain.
将压缩后的情报植入人类脑中
It's a different approach to body modification than our modern science.
这是一场不同于现代科学的人体实验
That is to say, Fire-breathing Bug shared between you
也就是说 你们身上的赴火之虫
is a pseudo-personality implanted by hypnosis.
是通过催眠术所植入的虚拟人格
Even though the original Fire-breathing Bug is long dead,
如今已经离世的那位最初的赴火之虫
that's how they propagated their personal will into the world.
就是靠这个办法 让自己的意识在这世上繁殖下去的
Is it not?
是这样吧
I see.
原来如…此
So somebody has finally figured it out.
有人…发现了…这个秘密吗
I didn't do it alone.
这并不是我一个人做到的
It was the work of those who came before me, pursuing various cases over the years.
这是不断调查各种事件的 前辈们所积累下来的成果
Though it sounds sarcastic saying that to you guys.
这些话对你来说就是一种讽刺吧
Worry not.
不必在意
You are…truly human.
你们…不愧是…人类
But how…will you prove…our crimes?
但…你们…要怎样… 证明…我们有罪
It'll be hard to explain, let alone prosecute
就你们至今为止所引起的 纵火事件来说
you guys for all the arson you've committed.
我恐怕很难对此做出说明或起诉
Then why…have you…come here?
那么…你为什么… 会来…这里
Even if I can't arrest you,
就算不能逮捕你们
I can at least stop you from committing future crimes is my thinking.
但我认为这样至少能阻止 今后会发生的事件
It's the crime of aiding and abetting.
我想说的是协同犯罪的罪名
You're connected to Solitaire, aren't you?
你们跟那家伙有关吧
We're the investigation unit assigned to tracking down Solitaire.
我们现在是负责调查雪天鸦的搜查班
Come on, show me.
来吧 让我见识一下
The power that turns this world upside down.
这个世界翻天覆地的瞬间吧
What's wrong?
怎么了
Someone's making a hell of a lot of noise somewhere.
不知道从哪里传来了 很激烈的打斗声
I'll go on ahead, Lulu.
我先走了 露露
O-Okay.
好 好
These primitive spells only unleash his magic in bursts,
仅仅只是将魔力释放出来的原始魔法
it's odd he would choose such basic attacks.
就算只是随意施法 这也太奇怪了
The protection of his body fortification is no joke.
他明明很擅长强化身体
But all of his other spells are like those of a novice.
可在其他方面他就像是新手一样
Necromancer, I really hit the jackpot with you.
死灵术士 你真是太合我胃口了
But you say you won't be my friend?
可你却不答应跟我交朋友
And what you're after is a peaceful life?
而且你居然还说 你想要的是安稳的生活
Even though you possess such power? What a sick joke!
如此强大的你 竟然会开这么低劣的玩笑
That may be so.
也许你说得并没有错
But I also don't intend to stop.
但我是不会放弃的
I won't let you interfere with this world
我不会让你威胁到我弟弟
where my friends and my little brother live.
和我的朋友所在的这个世界
That fortune-telling brat is impressive.
那个占卜师小鬼很有两下子嘛
Now, I have to go all out.
这下我也得拿出真正的实力了
Yes.
是啊
It might be better if you went all out to deal with that opponent instead.
你最好还是拿出全力对付那个家伙吧
Great. It's another brat.
喂喂 这边也是小鬼吗
Lord Civil?
塞维利亚大人
Almighty elf!
精灵大人
Please grant your protection to Lord Civil.
请保佑塞维利亚大人
Please, I beg you.
拜托了 拜托了
A warning from the great elf?
精灵大人的警告
I've never received such a strong warning before.
这么强烈的警告还是第一次
Found you.
找到你了
Give Polka
把波尔卡
back to me.
还给我吧
Ah.
啊
Ah, this is fantastic.
真是太棒了
You are fantastic.
你真是太棒了
This will only work out because it was you.
也只有你才能让我如此满意
It would be impossible for just any sorcerer to change the world.
区区一介魔法师是无法改变世界的
but you alone can revolutionize the world.
而你却可以凭一己之力 为这个世界带来变革
Your necromancy is proof of the existence of the soul.
你的死灵术就是灵魂存在的证明
So many powerful people
有不少的有权者
would rather become zombies to be immortal?
宁愿变成僵尸也想追求永恒的生命
If you make a pact with them, it'd be possible
如果与他们签订契约
to recast this boring world based on a completely new set of values!
就可以让这个无聊世界的价值观 变得焕然一新
And even if you don't want that to happen,
就算你不希望这种事发生
if you and I join forces,
只要你和我同心协力
we could bore a hole to the other side of the sky.
我们甚至可以打出一个 通往天空彼端的通道
And then we can go home!
然后我们就可以回去了
Leave this dull world behind.
我们就可以离开这个无聊的世界
To the world where you and I belong.
回到属于我们的世界去了
Whether you want it or not,
不管你愿不愿意
if you won't change the world,
如果你不改变世界
then there's no place for us here.
这里就没有我们的容身之处
That can't be…
怎么会
His magic is actually starting to come together.
他的魔法开始逐渐成形了
Thank you for showing me so much of your power.
谢谢你让我充分领悟你的力量
Thanks to you, I've gotten the hang of it.
多亏了你 我才能慢慢掌握这份力量
Of how to use that magic.
掌握该如何运用魔法
He was an amateur at magic until now.
他刚才明明还只是个 不懂魔法的外行人
But just by watching my technique?
只是看了我的术式 她就成长到这个地步了
He's a prodigy.
天才
Now, shall we lose the fireworks?
来吧 让我们奏响礼炮吧
In celebration of our meeting?
为了庆祝你与我之间的相遇
They use…fire like…a hundred years ago?
要像…一百年前…那样放一场火吗
Darn…Sabaramond.
可恶的…塞巴拉隆多
So this is the world the sorcerers from the other side had their sights on.
这就是你们这些异世界的魔法师们 所看到的世界吗
Elemental sorcery that doesn't make use of the elf.
无需精灵介入的元素魔法
That is a power not found in this world.
这是这个世界所没有的力量
Yes!
没错
A monster in possession of a power like this shouldn't be here!
拥有如此恐怖力量的怪物 是不能待在这里的
You and I should either go back there,
你是要和我一起回到那个世界
or change the world here.
还是要和我一起改变这个世界呢
Come on, let's completely change this world.
来吧 彻底改变这个世界吧
You already accomplished that once before.
你已经成功过了吧
Corpse God.
尸神殿
Or should I call you
不 我应该这样称呼你才对
"Emperor Killer",
弑君者
Rizdilusia Redrazalf.
利兹迪鲁夏雷托拉沙鲁夫
So you know about that too.
你连这件事都知道吗
I read the accounts of the Byandy Empire's main combat force again and again.
我多次在资料里看到过 有关巴亚蒂帝国主要战力的资料
I was so enamored by it, my heart danced.
看得我心潮彭湃 甚至迷恋上了呢
I was born in that world,
我诞生于那个世界
but the story was like a fairy tale that I couldn't even touch.
可那个世界却像童话世界般遥不可及
Come on.
来吧
Show me more of the powers from the other side of the sky!
让我再多见识一下 来自天空彼端的力量吧
She's gradually adjusting to my speed and moves!
这家伙逐渐适应我的速度和动作了
My right hand is my trump card.
右手是我的杀手锏
If I can't put her down in one move,
如果不能一击解决她
she'll probably figure out how to counter it too.
恐怕就会被她看穿
How is it that he knows my go-to moves?
这家伙为什么会知道我出招的习惯
I can't believe training with
没想到跟那只老虎训练的成果
that tiger is paying off here.
居然会在这里派上用场
Their attack methods are very similar.
他们的攻击方式很相似
In fact, I'd say they're totally same.
不 应该说完全一样
She's a wild animal in the body of a human.
这家伙就是一只披着人皮的猛兽
That's why I feel like I have a higher chance of beating her
正因如此 相比于对付那只老虎
than I ever did with that tiger!
这次反而我更有胜算
She's not in the realm of unreasonable.
这家伙并非强得离谱
Unreasonable applies to Agakura Majiri and Lemmin…
离谱的是阿牙仓万姬理和旅鼠…
Great elf? Why?
精灵大人为什么…
So this is the power of the great elf?
这就是精灵大人的力量吗
Amazing, how should I put it?
真是厉害 该怎么说呢
The vibe you get when you go in for the kill or make an attack?
这就是杀气或攻击的气息吗
It's still my first time experiencing it.
我还是第一次见识到
U-Um…
那 那个…
Oh. I'm Misaki. Nice to meet you.
对了 我叫美咲哦 请多指教
Sorry to be so direct,
我就直说了
but would you mind giving back that shark?
可以把请你把那个鲨鱼玩偶还给我吗
HOLD TIGHT
(抱紧)
No!
这可不行
Protecting this is the task I've been given.
我被赋予的使命就是保护它
Thought so.
我想也是
Okay. In other words, unless I get past this,
这样啊 也就是说 如果不通过这一关
I can't save the real Polka, I guess!
我就没办法救回真正的波尔卡了呢
Oh, crap. Can she deal with this?
可恶 这真的有办法对付吗
Can you do anything about this, Polka?
你真的有办法应对这一切吗 波尔卡
-Just as you said. -Huh?
-正如你所说 -啊
Both you and I are being incompatible with this world.
说到底 你和我 都与这个世界格格不入
And it's my fault, as a foreign entity in this world,
而且都是因为我这个外来者的存在
that elf with power that could destroy the city,
才会让可能会破坏这个城市的精灵
and you, a person who possesses abilities from another world
还有拥有异世界力量的你
were called here.
也来到了这个城市
That being the case, I'll end you here and return this body to Polka.
那么 我就在此阻止你 并将身体还给波尔卡吧
Once I've gone away somewhere,
然后如果我就这样消失在某处的话
the city will return to peace.
城市就会恢复和平
I don't know what those texts you read had to say about me,
虽然我不知道你读过的资料中 是怎么描述我的
but this place isn't a fairy tale.
但这里并不是童话世界
You will regret you ever met me.
吾会让你后悔见到我的
Both the name and the status of Corpse God
吾的名字和阶级
have fallen to waste already, along with the country.
早就已经随国家一同破灭了
All that remains is the immortal soul.
剩下的只有不死的灵魂
I'm used to playing the enemy of the world.
吾早已习惯与世界为敌了
(Episode 24: The Shinjuku War)
(#24 The Shinjuku War-新宿大战-)